You’re like a mirage that is almost within my grasp
Woo woo woo woo woo woo
I’m going crazy everyday thinking about you
I’m addicted to your love
I’m on fire
I can’t stop this burning heart
Deep into it
I want to slowly fall into you
This is addiction
I just can’t get enough
I’m divin’ and all in to you
I can’t get out of this attraction
You’re the one that I’ve been waiting for
The more I look at you, the more beautiful you are
You’re the sun, so I can’t hide you
Even if I lost my sight
Go straight to you
Ooh
Straight
Go straight to you
Ooh
Straight
Pedal to the metal hoo
Go straight to you I’m crazy in love
Everyone else, get out of my way
My other half showed up in the east
I fall in to the dazzling smile
I’m different from those who get lost easily
A step that won’t go wrong
The answer is already decided on you
I have no choice Wassup!
Just go straight No rules, No guides
(Oh god)
Add fuel to my emotions
Double for my heart engine Go vroom
I’m on fire
I can’t stop this burning heart
Deep into it
I want to slowly fall into you
This is addiction
I just can’t get enough
I’m divin’ and all in to you
I can’t get out of this attraction
You’re the one that I’ve been waiting for
The more I look at you, the more beautiful you are
You’re the sun, so I can’t hide you
Even if I lost my sight
Go straight to you
Ooh
Straight
Go straight to you
Ooh
Straight
Pedal to the metal hoo
Can’t nobody see us We’re up in the sky
Only awake the instincts, reason doesn’t matter
We gon’ ride Shout out to the end of the earth
Hold my hands tight No turning back
Go straight to you
Ooh
Pedal to the metal hoo
Go straight to you
Don't stop Just look forward and rush
Oh let's go
Pedal to the metal hoo
Won't stop Just look forward and go straight
Oh let's go
Go straight to you